Anuj Kumar Tiwari

Business Analyst

Contact

Address

Sector 69, Noida, DL, 201307

Phone

903 961 3546

E-mail

anujnau8844@gmail.com

LinkedIn

https://www.linkedin.com/in/anuj-tiwari-2a228b1a3/

Skills

Research and analysis

Time Series Analysis

Data collection and analysis

Data Analytics

Market Research

Predictive Modeling

Operations management

Software

Python

MIS Executive with over 1 years of successful experience in Data Analysis and Reporting. Recognized consistently for performance excellence and contributions to success in hospitality and IT industry. Strengths in Data Science and Statistical Analysis backed by training in Finance and Business Analytics.

Work History

2019-06 -Current

Executive

Oravel Stay Private Limited (OYO Rooms), Gurgaon, Haryana

- Data Capturing, Data Importing from the cloud DataBase using SQL.
- Data Cleaning, performing Exploratory Data Analysis(EDA) using Python or Excel
- Automating Google sheet using JavaScript code
- Predictive analytics using Python or Excel
- Preparing reports and Dashboard using Tableau
- Presenting the data and insight in the format which can easily be understood by the managers or another team members

2020-03 -2020-05

Research Analyst

Data Bridge Marketing Research, Gurgaon

- Developed macros, special formulas and other actions to produce reliable and consistent statistical reviews.
- Organized paperwork, including participantinformed consent waivers and research scope documentation.
- Collected data on competitors, consumers and marketplace and consolidated data into presentations and reports.
- Prepared 3 reports in week contain average 200 pages each.
- Completed over 50 tests on Marketing research participants, recorded findings in Python and reported them to supervisors.
- Created over 100 research summaries and presented them to supervisors to advocate further research and funding.

Power Bi

Tableau

Advance Excel

HTML & CSS

SQL

Languages

English

Hindi

Education

2017-07 -	MBA: Business Anlaytics And Marketing
2019-05	Galgotias University - Noida
2013-08 - 2016-05	BBA: Information Technology
2012-04 -	Jiwaji University - Gwalior High School Diploma
2013-03	Kendriya Vidyalya No. 3 - Gwalior

Certifications

2020-03	Python For DataScience, DataCamp
2020-04	Complete Machine Learning and Data Science: Zero to Mastery, Udemy
2020-03	MySql For DataAnalytics, Udemy
2018-11	Business Intelligence Analyst, Udemy